dialpad.com 2006-11-18

# Dialpad Communications, Inc - Privacy Policy

Dialpad Communications, Inc. ("Dialpad") is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices.

Because this website wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. By displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, this website has agreed to notify you:

| 

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website. 
  2. How the information is used.
  3. With whom the information may be shared.
  4. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information. 
  5. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Dialpad's control.
  6. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

---|---  
  
The TrustE program covers only information that is collected through this website, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Dialpad by sending e-mail to [privacy@dialpad.com](mailto:privacy@dialpad.com). If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or if your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php>.  TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with Dialpad to resolve your concerns.

Dialpad is committed to protecting the information that you provide to us over the Internet. It is our policy to collect only the information that we require to process your order, and to provide service, support and information regarding your account. We only share your information with companies who help us to fulfill our obligation to you in providing you service. This privacy statement describes how we treat information received about you when you visit our website or register for Dialpad products or services. Please read our privacy policy carefully. By using this website or submitting any personal information, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Dialpad as described in this privacy policy. Also, please be aware that Dialpad may change this privacy policy from time to time. If we do choose to make a material change, we will send you an email to make you aware of these changes. Your continued use of our software and this website will constitute your consent to any such change. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance in registration for new registering users, and is otherwise effective on August 10, 2004 for all users. 

If you wish to change any of the information that you have provided to us, please enter your Dialpad login and password on our home page at www.dialpad.com and then access the My Account page.  Here you will have the opportunity to update all of your personal information. 

**Cookies**

Our website uses cookies to improve your experience at our site. Cookies manage Dialpad call sessions, provide customizable and personalized services and enhance your web viewing experience. Cookies are user-specific data that are sent by a web server and are stored on your computer. Cookies are created by the web server or the Java script in the HTML. When you visit Dialpad, cookies will be sent to your web browser by a web server, which can be later read by that server. We use cookies to: 

  1. Keep track of your session ID to allow you to securely login and manage your account.
  2. Measure certain aggregated traffic patterns of the Dialpad web site to enhance the service that we provide to you.
  3. Ensure that new users are able to sign up correctly.

We use cookies only for these objectives. Cookies cannot be used to get data from your hard drive, your email or any other personal data about you. We do not ask if you accept cookies or not on our website. However, if you set your web browser to not accept cookies, you cannot use our service.

In some cases our Ad Network will place clear gifs on our site in order to track the effectiveness of Dialpad's ads that appear on third party Web sites.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. This information is not tied to our customers' personally identifiable information. 

**Information Dialpad Gathers and Tracks**

We collect IP addresses to administer our website and diagnose problems. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. In addition, we collect information regarding log times, call duration, call numbers, country code and region code of our users for internal data analyses only. Such website usage information is not personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information is data about you that distinguishes you specifically such as first name and last name, email address, postal address, etc. 

Our website's registration process asks for contact information (such as name and email address), by which you can be personally identified. When you purchase products or services on our website, you will be asked for financial information, such as account or credit card numbers, as well as billing verification information, such as billing address. 

We do not target our services to children under the age of 18. We do not collect personal information from children under the age of 18 without parental consent. Minors under the age of 18 can only use our service with parental consent.

Dialpad values you as a customer and works diligently to protect your information. The information that you provide is never sold to third parties.

**How Dialpad Uses Information**

We use contact information from your registration form to contact you when necessary about issues concerning the use of our service. We collect and remember feedback that you provide to us, in order to troubleshoot in the event that you contact our customer support department. 

We use demographic and website usage information internally to improve the products and services we provide to you.

If you have provided credit card information, we will not use your credit card information for any purpose other than for processing payments. We use an outside credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes other than as described herein. 

We reserve the right to also use personally identifiable information to investigate and help prevent potentially unlawful activity that threatens either Dialpad, any company affiliated with Dialpad or the general public. Moreover, upon the appropriate request of a government agency, law enforcement, court or as otherwise required by law, Dialpad may disclose personally identifiable information.

We may send information to you from time to time regarding improvements to our services, or about new benefits related to your account. Also, on occasion it may be necessary for Dialpad to send out a service related announcement.  For instance, if our service will be temporarily suspended for maintenance, we may send you an email to that effect. You may not opt-out of these service related communications that enable us to provide information regarding service. 

**Choice/Opt-In**

You may choose to visit our website and not provide any information. If you do not provide any information to us, we will not have any information from you other than the information that the cookies send to your computer. If your cookies are turned off, we will not have any of your information but you will not be able to use our service. 

During the period between October 1999 and January 2003, Dialpad allowed its users to 'opt in' on our registration form to receive promotional emails from Dialpad and our partners.  At that time, users were given the ability to 'opt in' and to then complete a survey form that asked for specific demographic information.  This information has been shared with reputable third parties.  If you were a Dialpad user during this time and are receiving emails from any of these partners or from Dialpad and you wish to unsubscribe from their services, please follow the instructions contained in any promotional email to unsubscribe from receiving future promotional emails.  In addition, please send an email to [privacy@dialpad.com](mailto:privacy@dialpad.com) and include the email address to which you are receiving email and you will be removed from the Dialpad database and will not be included in any future data exchanges between Dialpad and our third party marketing partners.  Any email that is coming to you as a result of your having registered with Dialpad during that time period should have a clear and working link to allow you to unsubscribe; please report any such emails that do not to [privacy@dialpad.com](mailto:privacy@dialpad.com). 

**How Dialpad Protects Your Information**

Dialpad maintains high security measures to protect your information from loss, misuse or alteration. Information that we collect from you will be stored and backed up securely in an environmentally-controlled location. Only authorized people with user ID and password from Dialpad have access to the database. 

**Surveys and Sweepstakes**

From time to time, our website requests information from users via surveys or sweepstakes. Participation in these surveys or sweepstakes is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and address) and demographic information (such as age and zip code). Contact information will be used to notify sweepstakes winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for the purpose of monitoring or improving your use of, and satisfaction with, this website. 

**Public Forums**

From time to time, our website may contain public forums available to users. Please remember that any information you disclose in these areas becomes public information. You should take appropriate measures to protect your personally identifiable information. 

**Co-Branded Websites**

We sometimes enter into arrangements with third parties whereby we provide our services on their websites.  In many such cases, users will register for our service as well as that of the co-branded website.  We use your personally identifiable information and other general information in compliance with this privacy policy.  Our co-branding partners have their own privacy policies, which you should review since we do not have control over their privacy policies. 

**Email Links**

This website uses email links on the "Contact Us" page to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have.  We review every message received and try to respond promptly to each.  This information is used to respond directly to your questions or comments.  We may also file your comments to improve this website and the service, or we may review and discard the information. 

This website also contains links to other websites.  Dialpad is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites.  You are encouraged to review the privacy policies of these other websites before registering for any products or services from those websites. 

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, you can contact: 

Dialpad Communications, Inc.  
430 N. McCarthy Blvd, Suite 200  
Milpitas, California 95035
